<resources>
<string name="app_name">Credenz \'18</string>
<string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
<string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
<string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
<string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
<string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
<string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
<string name="credenzlogo">CredenzLogo</string>
<string name="bug_text">If you find a bug in this app or have more ideas for improvement, do not hesitate to contact us. We appreciate your support. Feel free to share your thoughts. Your suggestions are valuable to us.</string>



<!-- Event names -->
<string name="bplan">B-Plan</string>
<string name="contraption">Contraption</string>
<string name="clash">Clash</string>
<string name="cretronix">Cretronix</string>
<string name="datawiz">Datawiz</string>
<string name="enigma">Enigma</string>
<string name="nth">NTH</string>
<string name="paper">Paper Presentation</string>
<string name="pixelate">Pixelate</string>
<string name="quiz">Quiz</string>
<string name="roboliga">RoboLIGA</string>
<string name="rc">Reverse Coding</string>
<string name="software">Software Development</string>
<string name="wallstreet">Wallstreet</string>
<string name="web">Webweaver</string>
<string name="xodia">XOdia</string>


<!-- Structure -->
<string name="bplan_structure">At stage 1, the soft copy of the abstract (summary) should be submitted to bplan.credenz18@gmail.com\nThe Soft copy should be a .pdf file.\nEvaluation of Executive Summaries by judges and Short-listing of 7 (+3 waiting) business plans for the next stage takes place.\nEach team will be given 12 minutes in the final round to present their B-PLAN in College Auditorium in front of panel of judges and audience. A warning bell will be given at 10 minutes and a final 2 minutes thereafter.\nThe presentation would be followed by a question-answer session where they would be questioned on different hurdles, opportunities and obstacles at various points.\nThe main stress during question-answer session would be given on feasibility and Exit Plan.</string>
<string name="contraption_structure">1) Round 1:\nProblem statement will be released on the website 15 days prior to the event.\nParticipants have to mail there abstract to email id contraption.credenz18@gmail.com.\n2) Round 2: Best abstracts will be shortlisted from the first round. These teams will be allowed to come to college and demonstrate their machine and present their innovation.</string>
<string name="clash_structure">There will be TWO rounds per group:\nElimination Round (MCQ\'s Round)\nCoding Round (Final Round)\nOwing to the vast nature of the programming language, the event will be conducted in two categories, Junior Level and Senior Level.\nTeams can register at the registration desk on the day of the event, 1 hour prior to the event. Teams can also register at desks put up at various colleges in Pune.\nThe competition will test the participants\' programming skills and knowledge of C/C++.\nThe second round is a problem solving round where the participants are to code the solutions to the problems.\nNOTE: Only one computer will be provided to each team.</string>
<string name="cretronix_structure">Round 1: (Junior and Senior)\nIt will consist questions of following sections:\na. Riddles\nb. Numerical\nc. Find odd man out\nd. Crossword\ne. State full forms/ alternate names\nf. Find bugs from given circuit etc.\n(above sections are given just to get an idea about first round questions)\n\nRound 2: (Junior and Senior)\nThe participants will be given a problem statement and they are supposed to\nimplement the solution with the help of hardware components (simulation software\nproteus for senior round)</string>
<string name="datawiz_structure">The contest will be hosted on Kaggle.\nThe duration of the contest and the round structure will be released soon.\nOnce the problem statement(s) and the dataset(s) are released, the teams will have to solve the problem and submit the output file on the contest page in the stipulated amount of time. The submission file format will be specified on the contest page.</string>
<string name="enigma_structure">There will be three rounds.\nYou need to qualify the threshold score to get into the next round. The threshold will be decided based upon the performance of all the teams.\nNo mobile phones or any electronic gadgets are allowed during the event.\nThe decision of the organizer will be final.\nThere is no negative marking at any stage.\n\nRound 1:\nThere will be 35 questions in this round.\nTime limit is 30 minutes.\nFor every right answer you will be awarded points and no negative points for a wrong answer.\nThe marking scheme will be told on the day of the event.\n100 teams will qualify for the second round.\n\nRound 2:\nThere will be 15 questions in this round with a time constraint of 2 minutes for each question.\nEach team will be split in this round, and the players will play individually. Each player of a team will play for the same 15 questions.\nThe scoring will depend on the performance of both the participants.\nFor a question – If both members answer correctly, 4 points will be awarded. If one member answers correctly, 1 point will be awarded. No points will be awarded in any other case.\n25 teams will qualify for round 3.\n\nRound 3:\nThere will be 5 puzzles in this round.\nTime limit is 2 hours.\nYou need to claim whenever you are done.\nThe earliest claim with maximum right answers, wins.</string>
<string name="nth_structure">There will be two Network Treasure Hunts, three and one week respectively before Credenz \'18.\nBoth the Treasure Hunts are independent. There will be separate winners for both the Treasure Hunts.\nIt consists of 30 to 50 levels each.\nTo go to the next level, you need to crack the present level in any possible way.</string>
<string name="paper_structure">Only soft copy i.e. a .pdf file, of the paper and abstract should be submitted. The paper should not exceed more than 6 pages.\nSoft copy of the technical paper and the abstract should be mailed to paper.credenz18@gmail.com.\nThe paper must strictly adhere to the IEEE format.\nAuthors will get 15 minutes to deliver a presentation on their topic followed by a question - answer session.\nThe presentation should be in power point format (.ppt or .pptx).</string>
<string name="pixelate_structure">ROUND 1:\nEach team shall design a promotional poster based on the given theme which will be declared on our website 15 days before the event.\nThe date for sending the poster will be declared on the website.\nThe designs should be submitted in *.psd, *.cdr, *.ai, etc format.\nThe design submitted should not be flattened.\nThe brushes and fonts used should be mentioned in the documentation.\nAny external source or images used should also be included in the documentation.\n\nROUND 2:\nThe teams shall be given a topic to design a poster, on the spot.\nThe time allotted for this round will be 3 hours.\nYou can use the internet for 20 minutes during the competition. Specific time will be allotted for the same.\nYou are allowed to get your own brushes, fonts and textures. However, all this will be checked prior to you starting the competition.</string>
<string name="quiz_structure">There will be two rounds - one elimination rounds and one final round.\nDetails about structure of quiz will be provided at the time of the event.\nQuiz masters\' decision will be final on all matters\nRound 1 will be elimination round with no negative marking and round 2 will be conducted by quizmaster.\n\nRound 1: 25 questions\nFor this round we will keep database of 75 questions.\nFrom this 25 questions will be there in quiz offline paper.\n6 teams will be short listed for the second round.\n\nRound 2:\nThere will be 6 teams in the final round. The round will be conducted by the Quiz Master.</string>
<string name="roboliga_structure">The duration of each match will be 8 minutes (i.e. two halves, each of 4 minutes duration). A 30- seconds break will be given after half time during which the teams will be allowed to attend to their robots.\nEach match will be a one-on-one match between two similar teams selected randomly. For scoring system, refer to 8.A.\nThe team with the highest number of points is the winner of the match. In case of a tie, a penalty shootout will be held, details of which will be announced at the time of the event.\nThe field will be subjected to changes after the elimination rounds. The field design for final rounds will be revealed on the website before the final rounds.\nThe teams will be short-listed for final rounds on the basis of their score in the elimination round.\nElimination round:\nI. Goal from inner circle: +20 points.\nII. Goal from between inner circle and half line: +40 points\nIII. Goal from beyond half line: +60 points.\nIV. Negative points for Yellow Cards and fouls.\nV. Disqualification on Red Card.\nNote: This may change at the time of the event.\nFinal round: To be declared after elimination round.</string>
<string name="rc_structure">There are two rounds:\nLogic Round.\nDecipher and Code Round.\nLogic round consists of Logical questions which can be solved by coding.\nIn the Decipher and coding round, the participants have to write the code for pattern that maps input to output.\nThe event will be conducted in two categories, Junior level(First and Second year) and Senior level(Third and Fourth year).
</string>
<string name="software_structure">Participants will have to showcase their software applications on the day of event (i.e. Credenz \'18).\nWinners will be declared once all applications have been reviewed by judges.</string>
<string name="wallstreet_structure">The event will be conducted within PICT campus on all 3 days.\nParticipants will have to come to college campus to collect their account credentials after which they can play game from anywhere.\nEvery participant will be given virtual money to trade on our virtual stock market.\nThe event will be conducted on our Android App/Website.\nMock NEWS will be flashed regarding listed companies and their sectors based on which participants will buy/sell stocks to ultimately become the biggest gainer.\nConcepts such as IPO, short selling and high frequency trading will be inculcated within the event.\n
</string>
<string name="web_structure">1st ROUND:\nA problem statement shall be given to the participants online.\nThe problem statement shall be released approximately 20 Days prior on the official website of Credenz \'18.\nThe team should mail the files to webweaver.credenz17@gmail.com in zip archive. (All files with understandable documentation.)\n\n2nd ROUND\nThe second round shall be conducted at PICT.\nApproximately 10 teams shall be shortlisted.\nThe teams shall be given certain add-ons over the pages designed earlier.\nFive add-ons shall be given, specific to the pages designed by the participants.</string>
<string name="xodia_structure">Submission Procedure: The programmed bots have to be submitted on the website by the last day of submission given on the website.\nThe rules of the game and details of the interaction of the bot will be with the game description on the Website.</string>



<!--intro -->
<string name="bplan_intro">This event, also known as Business Plan, is an opportunity for all young minds with a spark, who aim to become entrepreneurs in the near future, to THINK big and prove it to the world. It will certainly be a good opportunity to have discussions with students, just as ambitious as you, and the well-learned people who can provide valuable guidance. Come, step forward and present your innovative ideas to a distinguished panel of judges.\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹150 for Non-IEEE members\n₹120 for IEEE members</string>
<string name="contraption_intro">Have you ever wondered how to apply toothpaste on your brush in 20 steps? Ever wondered how to light a candle in 30 steps? Contraption is all about complexifying the simplest of things you see around yourself. Its whole essence lies in a perfectly balanced mix of innovation, creativity, relevance which results in profound entertainment.\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹200 for Non-IEEE members\n₹180 for IEEE members
</string>
<string name="clash_intro">A C/C++ coding competition held in high regard for the conceptual challenges it brings to a coder\'s mind, \'C\'-LASH beckons all the programmers out there, amateur and experienced alike, to participate and enhance their coding skills! Utterly professional yet non-compromising on coding-fun, \'C\'-LASH tests you for your speed, logic and checks if you have the right outlook towards a problem. So \'compile\' yourself and join this national-level coding combat in Credenz \'18!\n\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹100 for Non-IEEE members\n₹80 for IEEE members</string>
<string name="cretronix_intro">An Electronics based competition which tests the participants\' theoretical and practical\nknowledge. (all students from FE to BE.)\n\nRegistration fees:\nRs.150 for Non-IEEE member\nRs. 120 for IEEE member </string>
<string name="datawiz_intro">DataWiz challenges you to find unconventional answers to real-world problems by applying the principles of probability, statistics and machine learning. Your goal is to analyse the data, algorithmically decipher the inherent patterns in the data and make predictions based on the statistical dependencies between the input and the corresponding output.\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹100 for Non-IEEE members\n₹80 for IEEE members</string>
<string name="enigma_intro">Do you have what it takes to face the mind boggling questions which will push your logical reasoning to its limit? Then don\'t miss on this amazing opportunity.\nEnigma is a logical reasoning based questionnaire, which will test your aptitude, thinking capability, response time and mental agility.\nSo get ready to put your Grey Cells to work!\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹50 for Non-IEEE members\n₹40 for IEEE members</string>
<string name="nth_intro">Hook onto Network Treasure Hunt, an online treasure hunt where participants follow clues and visit different websites to solve riddles. Solve a series of strategic clues to complete the track and win prizes. Decrypt rules, follow the trail and race to the finish to win exciting goodies! This is your chance to challenge your technical skills. So go on, login and be Sherlock for a day!\nTo start your hunt, go to www.nth.credenz.info\n\nRegistration Fees:\nFree</string>
<string name="paper_intro">It is always said that knowledge is not something to be confined to oneself, but something to be shared as much as possible. One of the most popular events of Credenz, Paper Presentation gives a platform to undergraduate/postgraduate students to present technical papers. So, here is your chance to challenge your own skills of research and put forth your ideas on technology in front of an experienced panel of judges.\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹200 for Non-IEEE members\n₹180 for IEEE members</string>
<string name="pixelate_intro">Plot the pixels of your imagination on the virtual canvas! If you think you can carve your message with the fusion of colours, designs, words culminating into an elegant art, here is your chance. Integrate your creativity with technology and paint your ideas!\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹150 for Non-IEEE members\n₹120 for IEEE members</string>
<string name="quiz_intro">There is no measure for intelligence and wisdom. The closest we could reach was by defining an IQ. Fortunately each of us is gifted with this feature. The question is, till what extend we possess it.\nDiscover the scope of this feature by Setting out on a voyage through a sea of mind-boggling questions captained by a witty quizmaster. The Quiz is divided into following three categories:\nGeneral Quiz: It includes everything from robotics to politics. Test your GK!\nMELA Quiz: Movies Entertainment Literature and Arts (MELA) is all set to test your knowledge of literature, arts and entertainment. If you are an entertainment lover, this is for you!\nBiz Tech Quiz: If you are passionate about marketing, economics and business, then Biz Tech is the ultimate questionnaire you need to answer to test your knowledge.\nSo brace yourself for captivating this intriguing questionnaire whose answers might just be lying somewhere at the back of your mind.\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹50 for Non-IEEE members (for one quiz)\n₹40 for IEEE members (for one quiz)</string>
<string name="roboliga_intro">Football - The most breath-taking game becomes even more so when it\'s the robots that play the game! Bring your footballer-bot to the game and become a part of the most attractive of the events of Credenz \'18. As an event that surely keeps everyone\'s eyes transfixed on the field, RoboLIGA does not fail to entertain and teach at the same time. Explore the Robotics-aspect of Credenz and experience the extravagant thrill as you make your bot wade past the opponent and… that\'s right – SCORE!\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹200 for Non-IEEE members\n₹160 for IEEE members</string>
<string name="rc_intro">Given some sequence of steps, writing a code and getting the output is pretty easy! Want to try doing this in reverse way? If given some input and output, can you find the logic and sequence? Focusing less on concepts, all you need is your logical skill to decipher this "Black Box". Reverse Coding is a logical event which tests your basic logical skills along with pattern analysis and recognition as you play with the code. So, get ready to reverse code in Credenz \'18!\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹80 for Non-IEEE members\n₹60 for IEEE members</string>
<string name="software_intro">Software Development will be an Application Development Competition, Android, Desktop, or Web with no restriction on the choice of programming language used. You can use ANY existing programming language(s) to make your application. The application will be judged by experts in the software industry.\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹200 for Non-IEEE members\n₹160 for IEEE members
</string>
<string name="wallstreet_intro">Ever wondered how those blue collars sitting in their corner office make deals worth over billions of dollars? Also, ever wondered why is there so much chaos due to the fluctuations in Sensex? Here is a virtual stock market to get a glimpse of everything that happens on Dalal Street.\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹50 for Non-IEEE members\n₹40 for IEEE members</string>
<string name="web_intro">Think about what happens when you visit a website that is poorly designed as opposed to one that is clean, easy-to-use and modern? The look and feel of a website is critical to keep visitors engaged online. If you think you can do this, it\'s time for you to design such a site. A striking blend of technology, skill and CREATIVITY can help you win this competition. Develop a website captivating enough to grab the attention of your peers and an experienced panel of judges.\n\nRegistration Fees:\n₹150 for Non-IEEE members\n₹120 for IEEE members</string>
<string name="xodia_intro">This is a competition between two program code. The code can be programmed in Python. Two bots will play against each other in a match, which is carried out by a programmed Game-Judge. The details of the game will be put up on the XOdia\'18 website during Credenz.\nTime period for programming the bot: 15 days\n\nAllowed Languages: Python\n\nRegistration Fees:\nFree</string>


<!-- judge -->
<string name="bplan_judge">Innovation involved in the development of the idea and its practicality.\nOriginality and Patentability.\nTechnical feasibility.\nImplementation of the product.\nCost efficiency (if relevant).\nSuperiority of the product over existing products in market.\nParticipants will be judged on the basis of their business acumen and on how sustainable and innovative their solution is.\nThe decision of the judges will be final and shall be respected.</string>
<string name="contraption_judge">Design of your machine\nNumber of steps involved in it.\nNumber of different types of energy conversions involved.\nAesthetic of machine.\nPresentation.\nInnovation.\nWill test elementary knowledge of applied physics of team.\nInnovative and team management skills will also be tested.</string>
<string name="clash_judge">The competition will test participants programming skills and knowledge of C/C++.\nTime and cost efficiency of the code.</string>
<string name="cretronix_judge">Round 1: Each section carries different credits. No negative marking. Teams having score above score threshold will be selected for Round 2.\nRound 2: Credits will be given based on understanding problem statement, component selection,\npractical performance and explanation of implemented circuit.\nWinner and runner-up will be awarded.</string>
<string name="datawiz_judge">The submissions will be evaluated on the error metric decided for the given dataset. If any two teams perform equally well on the overall score, the tie will be broken by comparing the submission time of both the teams.</string>
<string name="enigma_judge">No Judging Criteria!</string>
<string name="nth_judge">The person who has cracked the highest number of levels wins.\nNOTE: In case of a tie, the one who has reached first on that level is the winner.</string>
<string name="paper_judge">Oratory and Presentation skills will be of prime importance.\nRelevance of the content in context with the chosen topic.Judge\'s decision will be final and binding on all.</string>
<string name="pixelate_judge">Creativity and originality of the design.\nDistinct features incorporated in the design.\nPersuasiveness of the design, i.e. the efficiency of the design to convey the required message.\nPhotoshop skills.\nLayering and masking.\nThe decision of the judges will be final and shall be respected.</string>
<string name="quiz_judge">No Judging Criteria!
</string>
<string name="roboliga_judge">A yellow card will be flashed on each hand touch after the first one. A maximum of three such cards will add up to a red card i.e. Disqualification.\nLosing teams may re-register to participate again in the elimination round. Registration fees would be Rs.150/- for this case. (Organizers reserve the rights to close the re-registrations at any point of time).\nOrganizers have the authority to disqualify any team for misconduct or disorderly behaviour. This team would not be allowed to re-register.\nOrganizers reserve the rights to make changes to the field design at any time without prior notification. Participants are requested to refer to the website regularly for any such changes.\nOrganizers\' decisions will be final and binding to all.</string>
<string name="rc_judge">The competition will test the participants\' logical and coding skills.\nTime and cost efficiency of the code will be tested in round 2.</string>
<string name="software_judge">Criteria for Judging would consist of multiple parameters:\nUser Interface\nUser friendliness\nDeployment Scenarios\nPresentability\nScenario Adaptability\nFeature Richness\nAnd a few more.\nScenario Adaptability: You might be asked to clarify the use of your application in certain scenarios, say What if this software needs to be used in a Library? Or on a Cruiser? Can you elaborate on how that can be accomplished? What if this needs to be deployed in Software Company\'s office? At a manager\'s desk?</string>
<string name="wallstreet_judge">Top 3 participants with Highest Capital at the end of Day 3 will be declared as winners.</string>
<string name="web_judge">Creativity and originality of the design.\nDistinct features incorporated in the design.\nNavigation through the site, how well the pages are interconnected.\nPersuasiveness of the design, the efficiency of the site to give primary information on the required theme.\nBased on the your Design, UI/UX and Development.\nAdditional points will be awarded for backend development.</string>
<string name="xodia_judge">The rules for scoring and deciding the winner will be mentioned on the website, with the game details.</string>



<!-- rules -->
<string name="bplan_rules">A maximum of three candidates per plan pursuing undergraduate/graduate/postgraduate program at their institution will be allowed per team.\nProposed business plan should not be in violation of any intellectual property rights.\nAll the participants should bring receipt and valid I-Cards while coming for the contest. No one without I-Card will be allowed for the contest and the team will be disqualified.</string>
<string name="contraption_rules">1) A team of max. four members is allowed to participate.\n2) Machine should be of dimensions 8ft x 8ft x 8ft (maximum).\n3) Minimum 10 steps should be involved to complete the task otherwise team will be disqualified. However there is no constrain on maximum no. of steps.\n4) Minimum 4 different energy conversion should be implemented in machine. Otherwise team will be disqualified.\n5) Machine should perform the task in maximum of 4 minutes.\n6) Machine should not take support of any of four walls and ceiling.\n7) Teams have to submit abstract and flowchart in prescribed format well before the deadline for first round.\n8) Maximum of three trials/chances will be given to any team. For every other chance/trial there will be deduction of points.\n9) For every next chance reset time of 15 mins will be given to team.\n10) Only one team member is allowed to interact with the machine once the evaluation has begun. This includes resetting the machine during the run. This means that only one person will be allowed inside the arena. However, if the team goes for another run, the restriction of one person inside the arena is uplifted until the machine is ready for the other run.\n11) That person will explain about the machine and each step going on to judges.\n12) Each step in the machine should be considered as the transfer of one energy into another .A step is considered to accomplish when there is energy transformation. Example ball coming down from the wedge and hitting the domino is consider a step. In this potential energy of ball gets changed into kinetic energy while coming down and when it hits the domino, it transfers its energy to domino.\n13) Identical transfers of energy in succession should be considered one step. For eg., a set of dominos falling into each other should be considered one step. While technically each single domino falling is a step, stating one hundred steps for hundred dominos is repetitive and against the spirit of Rube Goldberg.\n14) You can use any material for making of your machine provided in any case , they does not lead damage to arena and other machines. Otherwise it will lead to disqualification of team.\n15) Hazardous materials are not allowed and any gas or any explosives are also not allowed . However you can use matchstick if required provided it does not damage the arena and any other Machine.\n16) We will not provide you any material for making of your Machine. However basic stationary materials will be provided to you.\n17) If required extension boards will be provided to you.\nBut we would really appreciate if you bring of your own.\n18) Bring 2 copies of abstract when you perform in college.\n19) No live animal should be used.\n20) Organizers have the right to change a rule or all if they feel.</string>
<string name="clash_rules">A maximum of 2 candidates pursuing undergraduate program at their institution are allowed per team.\nAll the participants should bring receipt and valid I-Cards while coming for the contest. A participant without an I-Card will NOT be allowed for the contest and the respective team will be disqualified.</string>
<string name="cretronix_rules">Each team can consist of maximum 3 members.\nElectronic gadgets are not allowed.\nAll the participants should bring receipt and valid I-Cards while coming for the contest. No one without I-Card will be allowed for the contest and the team will be disqualified.</string>
<string name="datawiz_rules">A maximum of 2 candidates pursuing undergraduate program at their institution are allowed per team.\nDisclosing the code and data outside of the teams is prohibited and will lead to disqualification.\nUsing code from any external resource(s) is not permitted and will lead to disqualification.\nRound specific rules will be specified on the contest page.</string>
<string name="enigma_rules">A maximum of two candidates pursuing undergraduate/graduate program at their institution will be allowed per team.\nStudents with a valid I-Card will be allowed for the contest else will lead to disqualification. A team has to register itself at the registration desk at the time of the event.\nAll the participants should bring their receipts while coming for the event.</string>
<string name="nth_rules">Register to get your NTH username.\nYou will be directed to the starting page of the hunt.\nTo advance, crack the question, and put the answer in the URL:\nFROM\nhttp://www.nth.credenz.info/question.php\nTO\nhttp://www.nth.credenz.info/answer.php\nYou need to use Google for many of them to solve. Of course, that is where you search for everything you don\'t know.\nCheck the source of the pages, you\'ll get some important clues for hunting further. The titles may also give you clues.\nMost importantly, do not forget to have fun!</string>
<string name="paper_rules">A team of maximum three candidates pursuing undergraduate/postgraduate program are allowed.\nAll the participants should bring valid I-Cards while coming for the contest. No one without I-Card will be allowed for the contest and the team will be disqualified.</string>
<string name="pixelate_rules">A team of maximum two candidates pursuing undergraduate courses are allowed per team.\nEach of the teams should have their own laptops on the day of the event.\nAll the participants should bring receipt and valid I-Cards while coming for the contest. No one without I-Card will be allowed for the contest and the team will be disqualified.</string>
<string name="quiz_rules">A maximum of two candidates pursuing under graduate/graduate program at their institution will be allowed per team.\nTeams can register at desks put up at various colleges in and around Pune. No one without I-Card will be allowed for the contest and the team will be disqualified. A team has to register itself at registration desk at time of event, one hour prior to the event.\nTeams may re-register for another time slot.\nAll the participants should bring receipt and valid I-Cards while coming for the event.</string>
<string name="roboliga_rules">A maximum of 3 candidates pursuing undergraduate program in their institution are allowed per team.\nTeams can register at the desk put up in various colleges in and around Pune.\nTeams can also register at the registration desk on the day of the event, at least an hour prior to the event.\n\nROBOT LIMITATIONS\nMaximum robot dimensions: 30cm x 30 cm x 30 cm.\nMaximum weight 3.5 kg.\nPower specifications:\nMax Voltage: 12V (Normal Operation).[This time car batteries will be provided by the organizers or the participants are allowed to bring their own batteries.]\nThe robot cannot split into two independent parts.\nRobot should be manually controlled and wired.\nNo weapons (blades, spikes) of any kind are to be attached onto the robot.\nThe participants are allowed to use any number of actuators.\nThere should be no intentional damage done to the other robot by means of attacking wires, wheels, motors etc.\nNOTE: Any damage to the field or to the opposing robot would result in immediate disqualification of the team.</string>
<string name="rc_rules">A maximum of 2 candidates pursuing undergraduate program at their institution are allowed per team.\nAll the participants should bring their receipt and valid I-Cards while coming for the contest. A participant without an I-Card will NOT be allowed for the contest and the respective team will be disqualified.\nMarking scheme will be declared on spot.</string>
<string name="software_rules">Maximum of Three people in a team.\nAll the participants should bring receipt and valid I-Cards while coming for the contest. A single team member without an I-Card will result in the disqualification of the entire team.</string>
<string name="wallstreet_rules">Every Participating candidate should be pursuing Undergraduate/Graduate courses.\nAll the participants should bring valid I-Cards while coming for the contest. No one without I-Card will be allowed for the contest and the team will be disqualified.</string>
<string name="web_rules">A team of maximum 3 is permissible for the event.\nUse of any front end framework is permitted.\nYou are allowed to use any language but readymade template must not be used.\nWordpress is not allowed.\nAll teams shall have to get their own laptops on the day of the competition. It is advisable to get a high speed data card (even though net connection will be provided), for your convenience.\nAll the participants should bring receipt and valid I-Cards while coming for the contest. A single team member without an I-Card will result in the disqualification of the entire team.\n
</string>
<string name="xodia_rules">A single person is allowed to participate, no teams will be entertained and may lead to disqualification.\nParticipants need to provide required information on and as and when required.\nAny malicious activity encountered by the bot will lead to disqualification.\nParticipants are allowed to send modified/corrected codes before the last date of submission (Submission dates will be released on the website). Any request for modification of code will not be entertained after that.</string>
<string name="ping">P.I.N.G. (PICT IEEE Newsletter Group) is the official technical magazine of PISB published twice a year. P.I.N.G. serves as a platform for individuals to portray their technical ingenuity. It highlights articles on cutting-edge technologies from technocrats all around the globe including students, industrialists and faculty members. It also features interviews of distinguished personalities in various technical domains.\nP.I.N.G. aims at keeping its readers up to date on recent developments in technology and helps them extrapolate their perceptions to contemporary ideas of modernisation.\n
</string>


    <!--Contacts -->

    <string name="enigma_contact">Shubham Runwal:   +91-9028048467\nMahima Hotchandni:  +91-9075422260</string>

    <string name="web_contact">Dhairyasheel Sutar:    +91-8788332232\nEvleen Singh:   +91-8446664813</string>

    <string name="wallstreet_contact">Hemang Pandit:    +91-8669109182\nPrajwal Chandak:   +91-8208812625</string>

    <string name="roboliga_contact">Lokesh Agrawal:   +91-9421495709\nMonesh Bansal:   +91-8390728956</string>

    <string name="quiz_contact">Hemang Pandit:    +91-8669109182\nShubham Runwal:   +91-9028048467</string>

    <string name="bplan_contact">Deepak Choudhary:   +91-8668229164\nGaurav Kale:   +91-7756912076</string>

    <string name="nth_contact">Aditi Kulkarni:   +91-8108590333\nToshal Agarwal:   +91-9545588430</string>

    <string name="datawiz_contact">Pranav Budhwant:   +91-7020991301\nNeeraj Panse:   +91-7767878679</string>

    <string name="software_contact">Shreyas Garsund:    +91-7774008206\nKush Teppalwar:   +91-8154957061</string>

    <string name="cretronix_contact">Riya Warkharkar:   +91-8308607640\nPrachi Kanakdande:   +91-7038328362</string>

    <string name="clash_contact">Ayush Gupta:   +91-9028600226\nAmey Deshpande:   +91-7588758032</string>

    <string name="contraption_contact">Isha Chidrawar:   +91-9604985621\nMrugakshi Chidrawar:   +91-9767790896</string>

    <string name="paper_contact">Vedang Mandhana:   +91-9561688777\nShubham Sundrani:   +91-9623888503</string>

    <string name="pixelate_contact">Deepak Choudhary:   +91-8668229164\nIsha Chidrawar:   +91-9604985621</string>

    <string name="rc_contact">Yakshit Jain:    +91-8087550042\nOmkar Patil:   +91-9922993249</string>

    <string name="xodia_contact">Shubham Sundrani:    +91-9623888503\nVedang Mandhana:   +91-9561688777</string>
    <string name="getping"><u>GET YOUR P.I.N.G. ISSUES HERE!</u></string>


    <string name="question">
        <b>Junior Category</b>\n\nDesign a Mobile Application or Web Based Application for any one of the following problem statements:\n\n1) Design and implement an application which helps users find out about the various events (eg. Stand up, dramas, flee markets, concerts, sports, other events) taking place in a city(eg. Pune). The categories of events can be decided by the developer.\n2) Design and implement an application for artists and art lovers. The application will be a platform for artists such as painters, sculptors, musicians, graphic designers etc to showcase their talents in their respective fields. The app also enables art connoisseurs to view the art, contact the artist and buy their art. Authentication and piracy related issues should be taken into consideration by the developer.\n3)Design and implement an application for senior citizens to aid and assist them effectively. Your application should have tracking features, emergency services, ease of use for the aged and all necessary tools viable from a Senior Citizen’s perspective. Additional functionalities may be added as deemed fit by the developer.\n4) Design and implement an App/Website of your choice.\nThe Application Should serve a meaningful and sound purpose. It would be judged on it’s Efficiency, Calibre, Usability and Practical Feasibility. The judges may request the Participants to justify their app with use case scenarios and cross questions. The Ultimate Decision of the Judges will be final and Binding in all cases.\n\n<b>Senior Category</b>\nDomains\n\n1) Internet of Things\n2) Machine Learning\n3) Cyber Security\n4) Graphical/Image Processing\n5) Cloud Computing\n6) Big Data Analytics\n7) Data Mining\n8) Blockchain\n\nThe Participants are expected to implement at least one of the above mentioned technologies in the Application they would be developing, which would either be a Mobile Application or a Computer Software or a Web Based Application. The Application Should Serve A Reasonable and Sound Technical Purpose. It would be Judged on it\’s Efficiency, Usability, Calibre and Practical Feasibility.\nAdditionally The Judges may request the Participants to justify their Application with some Use Case Scenario\’s and also Catechize Them Over The Same.\nThe Ultimate Decision of the Judges will be considered to be Final and Binding in all cases.
    </string>
    <string name="about_us">Credenz is the annual technical symposium organised by the PICT IEEE Student Branch. Started in 2004, with a view to elicit the best out of each and every one, it has grown to become one of the finest technical events today. Credenz aims not only to infuse a competitive spirit among participants, but also widen their horizons in the ever-changing field of technology via myriad seminars and workshops. Participants get a chance to discover their talents, and thrive in numerous events like Clash, Bplan, RoboLIGA, WebWeaver, Pixelate, Cretronix, Paper Presentation and DataWiz.
This is a unique chance for the students to go beyond the traditional spheres of academics, and make the most of their potential. It was this spirit of learning and discovery that inspired the team to put the entire social experience of the event online in \2009, through the arduous time of the swine flu which made social gatherings impossible. Following this great legacy, the team took Credenz ’10 to a whole new level, and now the PICT IEEE Student Branch presents to you Credenz ’18, a podium for you to nurture and cultivate your talents.</string>
</resources>
